[{"question": " i mean, i don\u0092t feel like i even have a girlfriend anymore.", "answer": " you want me to just quit my job so that you can feel like you\u0092ve got a girlfriend?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " is this about mark?", "answer": "  oh my god.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " okay, it\u0092s not, it\u0092s not.", "answer": " oh my god. i cannot keep having this same fight with you ross! look, urrgh, maybe we should take a break.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " then, we had this big, stupid fight, and i said i wanted to take a break, i don\u0092t want to take a break.", "answer": "  i\u0092ve been thinking, this is crazy, i mean don\u0092t, don\u0092t you think we can work on this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " hey, what do you want to drink?", "answer": " who\u0092s that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " nobody.", "answer": " is that mark?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " umm, honey, look he just came over to....", "answer": " yeah! got it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " how\u0092s the big anniversary dinner?", "answer": " well, we never actually got to dinner.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " ohhh, nice.", "answer": " no, we kinda broke up instead.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": "  god, monica it\u0092s on the ceiling.", "answer": " that\u0092s okay, this is more important than fruit   on my ceiling! you broke up?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " yeah, but it\u0092s okay, because when ross left mark came over.", "answer": " oh no!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " rachel, you and mark?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": "  hi, it\u0092s me. i\u0092ve been trying to reach you all night. i feel awful. please, ross, you gotta know there is nothing between me and mark. this whole break-up thing is just stupid.", "answer": " yeah!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " eh, i\u0092m just so sorry i put you through it. and, i y'know, i don\u0092t want to get back together over a machine.", "answer": " na-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " so, i love you.", "answer": " i love you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " and y'know what, i\u0092m gonna, i\u0092m gonna go to bed now, but ah, on my way to work tomorrow morning, i\u0092m gonna stop by around 8:30.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " chloe, chloe how\u0092s it coming?!!", "answer": "  hey, what kind of puppy do you think i should get?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " umm, oh, hey, i don\u0092t know. how about a big one?", "answer": " but my apartment is so...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " well then a small one!! listen, let\u0092s, we kinda have to get going!", "answer": " wait! where\u0092s my shoes?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " do i know why we\u0092re rushing?", "answer": " yeah, y'know the ah, the girlfriend i told you about last night?  well it turns out she ah, she wants to get back together with me. oh, i found it!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " that\u0092s so great for you guys!", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " you must be so happy!", "answer": " yes, yes i am, one of the many things i\u0092m feeling. well....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " good luck, with your girlfriend.", "answer": " oh, thank you.  hey, hey.  rachel!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " hi. ohhh, you got my message.", "answer": " yeah, oh hey, you are right on time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " so what do you say? can i be your girlfriend again?", "answer": " yes, you can, very much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " hey, why are you mopping your ceiling?", "answer": " oh, there\u0092s banana on it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " wow, i have the spirit of an old indian women living in mine.", "answer": " so then you know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " the mailman was downstairs, so i brought up your mail.", "answer": " oh, good. thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " now what is fabutec?", "answer": " okay, all right don\u0092t judge me to much. okay? um, but i saw this info-mercial, and um, i swear to you i have never-ever bought anything on tv before, except for this mop. but there was this stuff on leg waxing, it just, it looked so amazing....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " waxine!!", "answer": " yes! have you seen it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " oh, it\u0092s incredible! i so want to be a waxine girl.", "answer": " i know!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " god. do think it really doesn\u0092t hurt? \u0091cause how can they do that?", "answer": " hello! organic substances recently discovered in the depths of the rain forest!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " oh my god! oh my god!", "answer": " yeah. we figured when we couldn\u0092t find you, you\u0092d gone home to make up with rachel. which is probably what you shoulda done. huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " you think?! god, i, ah, i\u0092m in hell. i mean what, what am i gonna do? rachel\u0092s all like, \u0091i love you and, and let\u0092s work on this.\u0092 and all i can think about is, \u0091what is she gonna do? what is she gonna say?\u0092 when i tell her what i did.", "answer": " well, before we answer that, i think we should address the more important question. how dumb are you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " what?! look, we\u0092re trying to rebuild a relationship here, right. how am i supposed to do that here, without being totally honest with each other?", "answer": " look, ross look, i\u0092m on board about this totally honesty thing, i am, just not about stuff that\u0092s gonna get you in trouble.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " he\u0092s right. nobody\u0092s gonna benefit, and you\u0092re just gonna hurt her.", "answer": " yeah, and there won\u0092t be a relationship left to rebuild.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " yeah, but don\u0092t you think....", "answer": " all right look, if you absolutely have to tell her, at least wait until the timing\u0092s right. and that\u0092s what deathbeds are for.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " all right, okay, now, we just have to make sure she doesn\u0092t find out some other way.  did you think about the trail?", "answer": " what trail?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": "  the trail from the woman you did it with to the woman you hope never finds out who did it!  you always have to think about the trail!", "answer": " oh, i-i don\u0092t think there\u0092s any trail.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": "  after applying the waxine and linen strips to leg number one,", "answer": " did that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " grasp one of the linen strips by its \u0091easy grab tab\u0092 and pull it off in one quick pain free motion.", "answer": " okay.  ow!!!!! ow-oh-oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " was it not pain-free?", "answer": " no. it was painful. oh my god , they should call it pain-zine, now with a little wax.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " huh, well, the girls in the satin nighties on the commercial don\u0092t seem to think it\u0092s that bad.", "answer": " that\u0092s because their nerves are probably deadened from being so stupid. but hey, y'know if you don\u0092t believe me, please, by my guest.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": "  ow-ow-ow-ow! oh my god!!!", "answer": " now, are you glad we didn\u0092t start with the bikini strips?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": "  chloe? hi..", "answer": " is this about me taking your watch?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " you took my watch?", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry, i do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " just you keep it, listen did you, did you tell anyone about us?", "answer": " oh no. i feel it isn\u0092t really anybody\u0092s business, y'know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " exactly. so you didn\u0092t, didn\u0092t mention anything to issac right?", "answer": " oh, well i tell issac everything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " you tell, of course you do. issac. issac. hey, issac. issac, hi! y'know we haven\u0092t actually met...", "answer": " you dog!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " yes, i suppose i am a dog. but issac, see i-i happen to have a girlfriend.", "answer": " oh right, that rachel chick from the coffee place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " yeah, that\u0092s the one. listen, i don\u0092t want to hurt her.", "answer": " oh, hey, man i know, doesn\u0092t matter how much we love \u0091em, monogamy is too cruel a rule.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " yeah. listen, can you keep this information to yourself?", "answer": " aw, no problem dude. y'know we got to look out for each other. we\u0092re the same, you and me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " actually, no, we\u0092re not.", "answer": " yeah, we are.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " no, we\u0092re not.", "answer": " yeah, we are.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " no, we\u0092re not!!", "answer": " okay, we\u0092re not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " right.", "answer": " but, we are.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " fine. i just need to know that you\u0092re not gonna tell your sister.", "answer": " i can promise not to tell her again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  jasmine?", "answer": " uh-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " we met at phoebe\u0092s birthday party, i\u0092m, i\u0092m ross geller.", "answer": " you did a bad thing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " yes, i did.", "answer": " very bad!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " very bad.", "answer": " very, very bad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " i\u0092m agreeing with you. did you, listen, did you happen to tell phoebe yet?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " okay, jasmine, please, please don\u0092t. i love my girlfriend very much, and i want more than anything to just work it out with her. okay?", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " thank you, thank you.", "answer": " but you should probably talk to my roommate, because i told him and he knows phoebe too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " gunther! gunther. gunther, please tell me you didn\u0092t say anything to rachel about me and the girl from the xerox place.", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry. was i not supposed to?  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " ow!", "answer": " oh!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " ow!! ow!!", "answer": " ow!!! monica and phoebe: ow!!!!!!! ow-ow-ow-ow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " we\u0092re all right.", "answer": " it\u0092s okay, it\u0092s okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " we\u0092re all right.", "answer": " we were just waxing our legs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " off?!!", "answer": " for your information, this happens to be a pain like no man will ever experience.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " yeah, well i don\u0092t think you can make that statement, unless you\u0092ve been kicked in an area that god only meant to be treated nicely.", "answer": " yeah, i-i think that women just have a lower threshold of pain than men, that\u0092s all. i mean, come on, it\u0092s just a little wax.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " oh, that\u0092s mature.", "answer": " okay, fine, so now what, i just pull it off?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " that\u0092s right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " i can\u0092t talk to you. i can\u0092t even look at you right now!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " nothing, nothing.", "answer": "  rachel said everything was okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": "  what, what are they talking about?", "answer": " rachel?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " just get away from me!", "answer": " no, it was a mistake! i made a mistake! okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " oh my god.", "answer": " oh, i knew something had to be wrong, because my fingernails did not grow at all yesterday.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " yeah, well, i guess they had a fight, and he got drunk....", "answer": " oh!!  you guys knew about this and you didn\u0092t tell us?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": "  y'know what, i want you to leave! get outta here!", "answer": " no!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " just get out! now!!", "answer": " no!! no!! i wanna stay. i wanna talk about this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " was she good?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " come on ross! you said you wanted to talk about it, let\u0092s talk about it!! how was she?", "answer": " she was...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " awful! horrible!", "answer": " she was not good. not good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " ewwwww!", "answer": " uh-oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " good different?", "answer": " nobody likes change.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " should we do something?", "answer": " yeah, never cheat on rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " i\u0092m sorry, okay, i\u0092m sorry. i wa-i was disgusted with myself, and this morning i was so, i was so upset and then i got your message and i was so happy, and all i wanted was to get her out of my apartment as fast as possible.", "answer": " whoa!! whoa, whoa, wait a minute. what time did your little friend leave?  oh my god. she was there? she was still there? she was in there, when i was in there?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " listen. oh hey, hey, the important thing was that she meant, she meant nothing to me!", "answer": " and yet she was worth jeopardising our relationship!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " look, i didn\u0092t think there was a relationship to jeopardise. i thought we were broken up.", "answer": " we were on a break!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " that, for all i knew would, could last forever. that to me is a break-up.", "answer": " you think you\u0092re gonna get out of this on a technicality?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " look, i\u0092m not trying to get out of anything, okay. i thought our relationship was dead!", "answer": " well, you sure had a hell of a time at the wake!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": "  what, what are you doing? you can\u0092t go out there.", "answer": " why not?!  i\u0092m hungry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " god! and to have to hear about it from gunther!!", "answer": " come on! like i wanted him to tell you, i ran all over the place trying to make sure that didn\u0092t happen!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " y'know what, i think we can go out there. i mean they have more important things to worry about.", "answer": " yeah, we\u0092ll be fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " don\u0092t you realise none of this would\u0092ve ever happened if i didn\u0092t think at that same moment you weren\u0092t having sex with mark?", "answer": " all right. let\u0092s say i had slept with mark. would you have been able to forgive me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": "  yes i would.", "answer": " you\u0092d be okay if you knew that mark had kissed me, and been naked with me, and made love to me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": "  yes.", "answer": " you knew that our hot, sweaty, writhing bodies were....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " what? come on rach, tell me what you\u0092re thinking?", "answer": " i\u0092m thinking, i\u0092m gonna order a pizza.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " oh man, pizza? i like pizza.  put olives on the pizza.", "answer": " we could eat the wax! it\u0092s organic.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " oh great, food with hair on it.", "answer": " no, not the used wax.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " hey, can i, can i get in on that? because i\u0092m kinda hungry myself.", "answer": " fine.  hi! yes, i\u0092d like to order a large pizza.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " no anchovies.", "answer": " with ah, extra anchovies.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " that\u0092s okay, i\u0092ll just pick \u0091em off.", "answer": " yeah, and could you please chop some up and just put it right there in the sauce?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " you can have the last piece, if you want.", "answer": " well, i should think so. you slept with someone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " they\u0092re gonna get through this, aren\u0092t they?", "answer": " yeah, come on, it\u0092s ross and rachel, they\u0092ve got too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " you think i need a new walk?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " well y'know, i\u0092ve been walking the same way since high school. y'know, y'know how some guys they walk into a room and everybody takes notice. i think i need a \u0091take notice\u0092 walk.", "answer": " are you actually saying these words?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " whoa-ho-ho!  yeah, okay.", "answer": " hey. it\u0092s three in the morning. they don\u0092t know that i\u0092ve come home yet. you notice how neither one of them are wondering where i am.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " y'know what, y'know what, i\u0092m-i\u0092m not the one that wanted that, that break, okay. you\u0092re the one that bailed on us. you\u0092re the one that, that ran when things got just a little rough!", "answer": " that\u0092s....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " that\u0092s what?!", "answer": " that is neither here nor there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " no ross!!  don\u0092t! you can\u0092t just kiss me and think you\u0092re gonna make it all go away, okay? it doesn\u0092t work that way. it doesn\u0092t just make it better. okay?", "answer": " okay, okay, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": "  i think you should go.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": "  i really think you need to go now.", "answer": "  okay, okay. this morning you said there was nothing so big that we couldn\u0092t work past it together...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 309, "asentId": 310}, {"question": " yeah, what the hell did i know!", "answer": " look, look, there\u0092s got to be a way we can work past this. okay,  i can\u0092t imagine, i can\u0092t imagine my life without you.  without, without these arms, and your face, and this heart. your good heart rach,  and, and....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}, {"question": " they\u0092ve been quiet for a long time.", "answer": " maybe she killed him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 319, "asentId": 320}, {"question": "  is that your new walk?", "answer": "  no, i really have to pee.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep16.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 323, "asentId": 324}]